vintagestickers.com 2017-09-15

# Privacy Policy

At Lori Ferber Collecgibles ", the privacy of our visitors is of great importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by the site, how it is used and safeguard your information.

Log Files 

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. The information we collect is used for internal review and is then discarded, used to improve the content of our Web page and help us understand such things as how our visitors reach our site, which pages are most popular and helps us come up with new ideas on how to improve our website for our customers. 

Cookies and Web Beacons 

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features. 

Although we rarely have done it, we might also use third party advertisements on our website which could include Google Adsense. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense occassionally. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited.

DoubleClick DART cookies 

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history . DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

We collect the e-mail addresses of visitors when you sign up for our free newsletter or when you order from us. We are not sharing any of those email addresses to any third party.

By visiting the external links shown in Link page of this site, visitors are stipulated with the Privacy Policy and Terms of Services of respective web sites they visits.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at lori@loriferber.com.
